Little magazine collection, 1956-1979
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Little Magazine Collection 1956-1979
MS 242
The collection consists of single issues, partial and complete runs of approximately 375 little magazines, published 1956-1979. The primary emphasis is on the arts, with the majority devoted to poetry. Most of the periodicals were published in the United States, with Canada, Mexico, England, Switzerland and France also represented. Includes one Arizona publication, the Stolen Paper Review.
16.25 linear ft.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Organization
This collection is organized into 1 series:
Little Magazine Collection, 1956-1979
Scope and Content Note
Alphabetical arrangement by title.
Additional materials at MS 159.
Access Terms
American literature -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
Little magazines -- Specimens.
American periodicals -- Specimens.
Poetry -- Collections -- Periodicals.
American poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
English poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
Latin American poetry -- Periodicals.
Canadian poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals.
1950-1974
1975-1999
Container List
- Series 1: Little Magazine Collection, 1956-1979
  - (Box 1)
    - Abyss, Somerville, Massachusetts. Spring, 1971
    - The Agni Review, Cambridge, Massachusetts. 1978
    - Akzente, Munich, Germany. February, 1965
    - A la Luz, Riverside, California. Otoño de 1974
    - Alcheringa, New York, NY, 1970-1976.
    - The Alley Cat Readings, Venice, CA. 1976
    - Amaranthus, Grand Rapids, Michigan. 1972
    - The American Pen, New York, NY 1972-1974
  - (Box 2)
    - American Review/ New American Review, New York and Toronto. 1967-1976
  - (Box 3)
    - Arcade, Allentown, Pennsylvania. no date
  - (Box 4)
    - Arions Dolphin, Cambridge, Massachusetts. 1971-1972
    - Ark III, San Francisco, California. Winter, 1957
    - The Ark River Review, Wichita, Kansas. 1973-1974
    - Art and Literature, Lausanne, Switzerland. Spring, 1965
    - Ascent, Urbana, Ill. no date
    - Attaboy, Boulder, Colorado. 1976
    - The Auden, New York, NY. 1956-1966
    - Audience, Boston, Massachusetts. 1971
    - Aura 6, Birmingham, Alabama Spring, 1977
    - The Aylesford Review, Aylesford, Kent. 1966-1967
    - Azu, New York, N.Y. November, 1970
    - Bachy, Los Angeles, California. 1972-1974
    - The Barat Review, Lake Forest, Illinois. no date
    - Bartleby's Review, Machias, Maine. 1972-1973
    - Before the Sun, Salem, Oregon. 1976
  - (Box 5)
    - The Beloit Poetry Journal, Beloit, Wisconsin. 1959-1966
    - Berkeley Bussei, Berkeley, Calif. 1955-1958
    - Bits, Cleveland, Ohio. 1975-1979
    - Black Cat Review, San Bernardino, Calif. March, 1963
    - Black Sun, Brooklyn, New York. 1965
    - Blank Tape, Brooklyn, New York. 1977
    - Bloodroot, Madison, Wisconsin. April, 1975
    - Bluestones, Woodstock, New York. 1964
    - The Book Exchange, London. December, 1971
    - The Book Review, San Francisco, California. 1970-1973
  - (Box 6)
    - Books Abroad, Norman, Oklahoma. 1969-1972
    - Boss, New York, NY. Spring, 1967
    - Boundary 2, Binghamton, New York 1972-1974
  - (Box 7)
    - Bricoleur, San Francisco, California. September, 1969
    - Brilliant Corners, Chicago, Illinois. 1975-1976
    - The Brown Bag, Greensboro, North Carolina. no date
    - Buffalo Stamps, Chicago, Illinois. 1973
    - Burning Water, Princeton, New Jersey. 1965
    - Cafeteria, San Diego, California. no date
    - Caim, Baltimore, Maryland. 1973-1974
    - The Cambridge Review, Cambridge, Massachusetts. 1956
    - The Capilano Review, Victoria, British Columbia. 1974
    - Caravan, Lamoni, Iowa. 1964
  - (Box 8)
    - Caterpillar, New York, N.Y. 1967-1972
    - Cave, Dunedin, New Zealand. 1979
    - Cedar Rock, New Braunfels, Texas. 1979
    - Celebration, Baltimore, Maryland. 1975
    - Celery, Kalamazoo, Michigan. 1977
    - Centennial Review, Ann Arbor, Michigan. 1973-1978
  - (Box 9)
    - Centering, East Lansing, Michigan. 1973-1978
    - Change, San Francisco, California. 1963
    - Chelsea, Gibraltar. 1964-1970
    - Chicago Review, Chicago, Illinois. 1958-1978
  - (Box 10)
    - Chidiock Amorphous, Richmond, Virginia. no date
    - Chinese Literature, Peking, China. 1963
    - Choice, Chicago, Illinois. 1961
    - Choomia, Framingham, Massachusetts. 1975
    - The Chowder Review, Madison, Wisconsin. 1975
    - Cimarron Review, Stillwater, Oklahoma. 1971-1972
    - Clown War, Brooklyn, New York. 1972
    - Coastlines, London, England. 1964
    - Cold Mountain Review, Boone, North Carolina. 1974-1978
    - Columbia Review, New York, NY. 1960-1965
    - Concerning Poetry, Bellingham, Washington. 1969
    - Contempora, Atlanta, Georgia. 1972
    - Contemporary Poetry, Teaneck, New Jersey. 1973
    - Copkiller, New Orleans, Louisiana. 1968
    - Corduroy, Newark, New Jersey. no date
    - Cornell, Review, Ithaca, New York. 1977-1979
  - (Box 11)
    - Cottonwood, Lawrence, Kansas. Fall, 1969
    - Counterweight Quarterly, Brooklyn, New York. 1966-1967
    - Crazy Horse 2, Fargo, North Dakota. 1967-1971
    - Crucible, Auckland, New Zealand. 1967
    - Cuchuiain, New York, NY. 1967
    - Dasein, New York, NY. 1965-1966
    - Delos, Austin, Texas. 1968-1969
    - Delto, Montreal, Canada. 1958
    - Denver Quarterly, Ann Arbor, Michigan. 1968
    - Descant, Fort Worth, Texas. 1968-1971
    - Dial-Og, Toronto, Canada. 1971-1973
    - Dogsoldier, Spokane, Washington. 1974
    - Down and Out, Tucumcari, New Mexico. October 31, 1974
    - Down Here, New York, NY. no date
    - The Dutton Review, New York, NY. 1970
    - Dying Gardens, New York, NY. no date
  - (Box 12)
    - Earth's Daughters, Buffalo, New York. February, 1971
    - East Side Review, New York, NY. 1966
    - El Corno Emplumado, Mexico City. 1964-1969
    - Elizabeth, New Rochelle, New York. 1964-1965
    - The Emerson Review, Hollywood, California. 1964-1965
    - Epoch, Ithaca, New York. 1962-1968
    - Epos, Crescent City, Florida. 1956-1973
    - Event, Victoria, British Columbia. 1972
    - Everyman, Cleveland, Ohio. Summer, 1974
  - (Box 13)
    - Evidence, Toronto, Canada. 1964-1967
    - Exile, Toronto, Canada. 1972
    - Faire, Walla Walla, Washington. 1975-1977
    - The Falcon, Mansfield, Pennsylvania. 1970-1976
  - (Box 14)
    - The Far Point, Winnipeg, Canada. 1969-1973
    - Fiction, New York, NY. 1978
    - Fiction International, Canton, New York. 1973-1976
    - The Fiddlehead, Frederiction, New Brunswick, Canada. 1965-1967
    - Field, Oberlin, Ohio. 1970-1973
    - First Person, Boston, Massachusetts. 1960-1961
  - (Box 15)
    - Folio, Birmingham, Alabama. 1969-1973
    - Free Poems Among Friends, Detroit, Michigan. 1965
    - Gadfly, Cambridge, Mass. 1953-1968
    - Gallows, Eureka, California. no date
    - Gegenschein, Pullman, Washington. 1972
    - Genesis West, Burlingame, California. 1962-1965
    - The Genre of Silence, New York, NY. 1967
    - Goosberry, Cleveland, Ohio. 1965
    - Gorilla, New York, NY. 1967
    - Gravida, 1973-1979
    - The Green Fuse, Broderick, California. 1977
    - The Greenfield Review. 1970-1974
    - Greenhouse Review, Santa Cruz, California. Spring, 1979
    - The Greensboro Review, Santa Cruz, California. Winter, 1973
  - (Box 16)
    - Grist, Lawrence, Kansas. no date
    - Grove, Claremont, California. Summer, 1975
    - Gulfstream, Baton Rouge, Louisiana. 1973
    - The Gypsy Scholar, East Lansing, Michigan. Winter, 1974
    - Haiku, Forest Hills, New York. June, 1967
    - Half n' Half. April, 1971
    - Hanging Loose, Traumansburg, New York. 1966-1967
    - The Harrison Street Review, Kansas City, Missouri. 1971-1972
    - Hawaii Review, Honolulu, Hawaii. 1973-1978
    - Heads Up, Haddonfield, New Jersey. Fall, 1967
    - Hearse, Eureka, California. 1969-1972
    - Helicon, Brooklyn, New York. 1964
    - Here it is, Chicago, Illinois. 1975
    - Hika, Gamier, Ohio. 1966-1968
    - Hog River Review. Fall, 1973
  - (Box 17)
    - The Hudson Review, New York, NY. Spring, 1975
    - I-Kon, New York, NY. 1967-1968
    - I.E., Cambridge, Massachusetts. no date
    - Illinois Quarterly, Normal, Illinois. 1974-1975
    - Imago, Calgary, Alberta, Canada. no date
    - In the Light, Barrington, Illinois. 1975-1976
    - In Transit, Bronx, NY. no date
    - The Interlochen Review, Interlochen, Michigan. Spring, 1978
    - Intrepid, Kenmore, New York. 1967-1972
  - (Box 18)
    - Intrinsic, Toronto, Canada. Summer, 1977
    - Intro, Hendel, & Reinke, Publishers. 1979
    - Io, Ann Arbor, Michigan. 1966-1968
    - Is, Toronto, Canada. 1969-1970
    - Jason, Willamette, Oregon. 1974
    - Jazz, Los Angeles, California. 1979
    - Jeopardy, Bellingham, Washington. 1969-1970
    - Joglars, Providence, Rhode Island. 1964-1966
    - Journal of Modern Literature, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. April, 1975
    - The Judson Review, Greenwich Village, New York. 1963
    - Kaleidoscope, Hermit Press. 1971
    - Kamadhenu, Pullman, Washington. 1972-1973
    - Karamu, Charleston, Illinois. 1976
  - (Box 19)
    - [Box 19, Kauri, was moved to PS508.N3 K3]
  - (Box 20)
    - Kayak, Santa Cruz, California. no date
    - Konglomerati, Gulfport, Florida. 1972
    - The Lamp in the Spine, Berkeley, California. 1974
    - The Lampeier Muse, Annandale-on-Hudson, New York. 1966-1972
    - The Lavrel Review, Bridgeport, Connecticut. 1967
    - Lemming, San Diego, California. 1971
  - (Box 21)
    - Lines, New York, NY. December, 1962-November, 1965
    - The Lit, Notre Dame, Indiana. 1968
    - Literary Circle, Chicago, Illinois. November, 1968
    - Literary Magazine, Medford, Massachusetts. Spring, 1968
    - The Literary Monitor, Sunnyvale, California. 1979
    - The Little Magazine, Nuttley, New Jersey. 1973
    - Living Hand, Salisbury, England. 1973
    - Local Tenderness, East Lansing, Michigan. 1974
    - Locus Solus, Geneva, Switzerland. 1961-1962
  - (Box 22)
    - Loose Change, Half-Ass Press. no date
    - Love, Berkeley, California. 1966
    - Lynx, Plainview, Texas. January, 1963
    - Maelstrom, New York, NY. 1966
    - Magazine, New York, NY. no date
    - Maine Edition, Topsham, Maine. November, 1973
    - Mango, San Jose, California. 1977
    - Manroot, South San Francisco, California. 1971
    - Margins, Milwaukee, Wisconsin. August-September, 1974
    - Marrahwanna Quarterly, Cleveland, Ohio. Winter, 1964-1965
    - Mass Transit, Washington, D.C. 1973
    - Massachusetts, Review, Amherst, Massachusetts. Winter, 1971
    - Mati, Chicago, Illinois. 1975-1976
  - (Box 23)
    - Mediterranean Review, Oakdale, New York. 1970-1973
    - Midwest, Chicago, Illinois. 1961-1962
    - Milk Quarterly, Chicago, Illinois. 1974-1975
    - Minnesota, Review, St. Paul, Minnesota. 1968-1972
    - Miscellany, Chestertown, Maryland. 1966-1968
    - Mississippi Valley Review, Macomb ,Illinois. 1975-1975
    - The Missouri Review, Columbia, Missouri. 1978-1979
  - (Box 24)
    - Mudflat Review, Colati, California. 1972
    - Mundus Artium, Athens, Ohio. 1974
    - Narcissus, Columbia, Missouri. Spring, 1979
    - New: American & Canadian Poetry, Trumansburg, New York. 1966-1967
    - The New Earth Review, Staton Island, New York. 1976
    - New Improved, Chicago, Illinois. 1964
    - New Letters, Kansas City, Missouri. 1972-1977
    - The New Oneota Review, Decorah, Iowa. Spring, 1974
    - The New Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska. Winter, 1972
    - New Wilderness Letter. 1977-1978
    - The New York Quarterly, New York, NY. 1970-1973
  - (Box 25)
    - Nimrod, Tulsa, Oklahoma. 1960-1972
    - Nine Queen Bees, Honolulu, Hawaii. no date
    - Niobe, Brooklyn Heights, New York. 1965-1966
    - Nommo, Chicago, Illinois. 1975
    - The North Stone Review, Minneapolis, Minnesota. 1973
    - Northwest Review, Eugene, Oregon. 1963-1975
    - Now, San Francisco, California. 1963-1965
    - Occurrence, Shippensburg, Pennsylvania. no date
    - Ohio Review, Athens, Ohio. 1973
  - (Box 26)
    - Ole, Bensenville, Illinois. 1965-1967
    - Omnivore, Forest Hills, New York. 1963
    - Openplaces, New York, NY 1967-1976
    - Opus, Albany, California. 1970
    - Original Sin, Putney, Vermont. Winter, 1977
    - Own Wister Review, Laramie, Wyoming. Fall, 1978
  - (Box 27)
    - Painted Bride Quarterly, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. 1973-1983
    - Pan, New York, NY. 1957-1958
    - Para Linguistics, New York, NY. Summer, 1966
    - Parasite, Paris, France. 1968
    - The Paris Revew, Paris, France. 1953-1975
    - Parnassus, New York, NY. 1972
    - Partisan Review, New Brunswick, New Jersey 1961-1971
    - Period One, Granville, Ohio. 1964
    - The Periodical Lunch, Ann Arbor, Michigan. 1975
    - Permafrost, Fairbanks, Alaska. 1977
  - (Box 28)
    - Perspective, St. Louis, Missouri. Winter, 1966
    - Plaintiff, Manhato, Minnestoa. 1968-1969
    - Poems of the People, Mt. Pleasant, Michigan. 1970
    - Poesie Vivante, Geneve, Suisse. 1966
    - Poet & Critic, Lafayette, Indiana. 1961-1962
    - Poetry, Pasadena, California. 1966
    - Poetry, Chicago, Illinois. 1967-1973
    - Poetry Australia, Sidney, Australia. June, 1969
    - The Poetry Miscellany, Williamstown, Massachusetts. 1971-1973
  - (Box 29)
    - Poetry Northwest, Seattle, Washington. 1962-1981
    - Poetry Public, Hastings, Nebraska. 1958
    - Poetry Review, Tampa, Florida. 1964-1967
    - Poetry Round Table, Hackensack, New Jersey. 1972
    - Poetry Toronto Newsletter, Toronto, Canada. 1976
    - Polaris, Ada, Ohio. Spring, 1972
    - Potpourri, Milwaukie, Oregon. Spring, 1967
    - Prairie Schooner, Lincoln, Nebraska. 1960-1970
    - Premiere, Lexington, Mass. 1967-1968
    - Promethean, New York, NY. 1965-1970
    - Prometheus, Watertown, New York. Spring, 1975
    - Prospetti, Rome, Italy. March, 1966
    - Protesta, Allentown, Pennsylvania. 1962
    - The Providence Review, San Francisco, California. 1974
    - Purchase Poetry Review. Spring, 1979
    - Pure Smutte, Ann Arbor, Michigan. 1972
  - (Box 30)
    - Purr, Los Angeles, California. 1975
    - The Quarterly Review, Annandale-on-Hudson, New York. 1967
    - Quarterly West, Salt Lake City, Utah. Autumn, 1977
    - Quartet, College Station, Texas. 1970-1971
    - Quetzal, Phantom Hill, Texas. 1970-1971
    - Raster, The Netherlands. 1971
    - Readers & Writers, Jamaica, New York. 1967
    - Red Balloon Poetry Conspiracy, Brooklyn, New York. May, 1976
    - Red Cedar Review, East Lansing, Michigan. 1973-1977
    - Red Canyon, Charlotte, North Carolina. 1969
    - Reflector. 1975-1976
    - Region, St. Paul, Minnesota. no date
    - Renaissance, San Francisco, California. 1962
    - Revista De, Mexico. 1968
  - (Box 31)
    - Rhymers' Club Magazine, Rohnert Park, California. 1971-1972
    - Riverrun, New York, NY. 1967
    - Rocky Mountain Creative Arts Journal, Casper, Wyoming. 1974-1976
    - Salmagundi, Flushing, New York. 1969-1970
    - Salted Feathers, Pullman Washington. 1964-1967
    - Sample Copy, Chapel Hill, North Carolina. 1968
    - San Marcos Review, Albuquerque, New Mexico. no date
    - Satori. Winter, 1968
    - Sawtooth, Twin Falls, Idaho. Spring, 1976
    - Schist, Willimantic, Connecticut. Fall, 1973
    - Scopcraeft, Fargo, North Dakota. May, 1971
    - Scree, Missoula, Montana. 1976-1981
  - (Box 32)
    - Scribe, Boston, Massachusetts. Winter, 1969
    - Seizre Magazine, Gresham, Oregon. 1974
    - The Sewanee Review, Knoxville, Tennessee. Spring, 1971
    - Shaded Room, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. March, 1970
    - Shamon, Kennebunk, Maine. 1973
    - Shankpainter, Provincetown, Massachusetts. 1970-1974
    - A Shout in the Street, Flushing, New York. 1976
    - Showcase, Barstow, California. 1965-1966
    - Silenus, Lake Forest, Illinois. 1975
  - (Box 33)
    - Simbolica, Tiburon, California. 1961
    - The Sinking Bear, New York, NY. 1964
    - Sixpack, Lake Toxaway, North Carolina. Winter, 1973/1974
    - The Small Pond Magazine, Stratford, Connecticut. 1966-1977
    - Small Press Review, Paradise, California. 1975
    - The Smiths, New York, NY. 1964-1968
    - Softball, Cambridge, Massachusetts. 1971
    - South, Deland, Florida. 1970
    - The South Dakota Review, Vermillion, South Dakota. 1966-1968
    - Southern Poetry Review, Raleigh, North Carolina. Spring, 1973
    - The Southern Review, Raleigh, North Carolina. 1968-1973
  - (Box 34)
    - Southwestern Review, Lafayette, Louisiana. Spring, 1976
    - Sou'wester, Edwardsville, Illinois. 1968-1976
    - Spindrift, Seattle, Washington. 1977
    - Stand, London, England. 1969
    - Stations, Milwaukee, Wisconsin. 1972-1974
    - Steelhead, Duluth, Minnesota. December, 1971
    - Sticks, & Stones, St. Cloud, Minnesota. Fall, 1970
    - Stolen Paper Review, Tempe, Arizona. Spring, 1963
    - Stone Country, Madison, New Jersey. 1979-1980
    - Stone Drum, Huntsville, Texas. 1972
    - Stonehinge, Hunstville, Texas. 1972
    - Stony Brook, Stony Brook, New York. 1968
    - Story Quarterly, Wheeling, Illinois. 1976
    - The Stray Shot. 1970
  - (Box 35)
    - Streets, New York, NY 1965
    - Studies in Contemporary, Satire, Cambridge, Springs, Pennsylvania.. 1974
    - Sumac, Fremont, Michigan. 1969-1971
    - Sun, New York, NY. 1971-1975
    - Sundial, New York, NY. 1971-1975
    - The Sunset Palms Hotel, Ocean Park Station, California. 1973-1974
    - The Survivor's Manual, Southampton, New York. January, 1972
    - Tarasque, Trent Bride, Nottingham, England. no date
    - Target, Peterborough. no date
    - Tempest, Milwaukee, Wisconsin. Spring, 1969
    - Le Temps des Loups, Paris, France. Winter, 1965
    - Tennessee Poetry Journal, Martin, Tennessee. Spring, 1970
    - Tens, Los Angeles, California. 1972
  - (Box 36)
    - Text, New York, NY. 1978-1979
    - 13th Moon, New York, NY. 1978
    - Thorn, New York, NY. 1965
    - Throb, Manhattan Beach, California. 1971
    - Tish, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada. 1962-1968
    - Tomorrow, Oxford. 1959-1960
    - Trace, Hollywood, California. 1962-1963
    - Tractor, Santa Barbara, California. 1972
    - Transatlantic, Review, New York, NY. 1965-1976
    - Transition, Cortland, New York. 1966-1969
    - Translation, New York, NY. 1973
  - (Box 37)
    - Tri-Quarterly, Evanston, Illinois. 1965-1976
    - Trobar, Brooklyn, New York. 1960-1964
    - Truck, Carrboro, North Carolina. Spring, 1976
    - Unfold, Folsom, California. 1972
    - Unicorn Journal, Santa Barbara, California. 1968-1969
    - Unmuzzled Ox, Brooklyn, New York. 1971-1972
    - Unnatural Acts, New York, NY. 1972
  - (Box 38)
    - Ut Review, Tampa, Florida. 1973-1974
    - Vegetable Bax, Cincinnati, Ohio. Spring, 1978
    - Verb, Denver, Colorado. August, 1966
    - Vincent, New York, NY. 1968
    - Virginia Quarterly, Richmond, Virginia. Autumn, 1972
    - Watu, Ithaca, New York. November, 1956
    - Wayne Literary Review, Detroit, Michigan. Spring, 1975
    - West Coast Review, Vancouver, British Columbia. 1970-1971
    - Westigan Review, Kalamazoo, Michigan. 1970-1977
  - (Box 39)
    - Whetstone, Huntsville, Texas. 1969-1971
    - White Dove Review, Tulsa, Oklahoma. 1959
    - Wild Dog, Pocatello, Idaho. 1964
    - Winged Ox, Rolla, Montana. Summer, 1975
    - Works, New York, NY. 1967-1971
    - The Wormwood Review, Storrs, Connecticut. 1962-1984
    - The Yale Literary Magazine, New Haven, Connecticut. April, 1965
    - Zehyrus, Bowling Green, Kentucky. 1969-1979